{
    "subject": "resource/Mathilde_Santing",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Amstelveen",
    "human_readable": "The birth place of Mathilde Santing is Amstelveen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9138357043266296,
            "question": "Is Mathilde Santing from Amstelveen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9040448665618896,
            "question": "Where was Mathilde Santing born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8857169151306152,
            "question": "What is the name of Mathilde Santing's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8842346668243408,
            "question": "What is the birthplace of Mathilde Santing called?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8678643703460693,
            "question": "Can you name the city that is Mathilde Santing's place of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8103450536727905,
            "question": "If you were to visit Mathilde Santing's birthplace, where would you go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.773874044418335,
            "question": "Amstelveen is associated with the birth of whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7581048607826233,
            "question": "Who was born in Amstelveen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6244123578071594,
            "question": "Where did Mathilde Santing originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47072967886924744,
            "question": "In which city did Mathilde Santing come into the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birth place of Mathilde Santing is Amstelveen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7555_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Mathilde Santing originate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7555_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was born in Amstelveen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7555_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Amstelveen is associated with the birth of whom?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7555_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7555_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7555_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7555_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7555_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7555_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7555_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7555_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7555_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7555_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7555_41.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Santing was born in Amstelveen, The Netherlands,\" which supports the query regarding Mathilde Santing's birthplace."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}